W12 W12 收到吗
Whiskey-1-2. Whiskey-1-2, do you copy?
准备掉头返回 快回话
Gonna 180, close the distance, get back in contact.
别慌 伙计们
Have faith, guys.
只是一点气流紊乱 再糟的我们都经历过
I've got us through a lot worse than some light turbulence.
稳住
Hold on!
- 韦尔斯 - 求救 求救
- Wellsey! - Mayday, Mayday, Mayday!
准备坠落
Crash positions!
我尽力降落在公路上
I'm putting her down by the road.
快点
Come on.
要撞了
We're going in hard!
《行尸走肉》
别勉强
Don't push yourself.
你坐会吧
You'd better sit.
我去看看
I'll check it out.
有人来了
Someone's coming.
- 有生还的吗 - 有两具尸体 其他不明
- Any survivors? - Two dead, not sure about the other.
散开
Fan out.
别浪费子弹 除非万不得已
Save those rounds until you need 'em.
还有人活着 提姆
Got a breather. Tim!
帮我一下
Help me out here.
不
No.
这边 香珀特
Over here, Shumpert.
搬他出来
Drag him out.
他在救他们 我们该现身
He's saving them. We should show ourselves.
还不行
Not yet.
我们走吧
Let's roll out.
姑娘放松
Easy does it, girl.
我的武器可比你厉害
Mine's a whole lot bigger than yours.
现在放下刀
Now put down your weapons.
没错 慢慢来
That's it. Nice and easy.
手举起来
And let me see your hands.
转过来 没错
Now spin around. That's it.
慢慢转
Nice little twirl around.
活见鬼了
Oh, holy shit.
金发美女
Blondie.
你看起来还不错
Damn, you're looking good.
不给老朋友莫尔一个拥抱吗
Now, how's about a big hug for your old pal Merle?
让斯蒂文斯准备医疗室
Have Stevens prep the infirmary.
- 几名伤者 - 三名
- How many? - Three.
一人多处骨折加严重烧伤
One with multiple fractures and severe burns.
还有个时醒时晕
Another in and out of consciousness,
应该是受了惊吓加脱水
probably shock and dehydration.
- 第三人呢 - 她很好
- And the third? - She's fine.
- 是女的吗 - 两个呢
- A female? - Two.
发现她们躲在树林里
Found them hiding in the woods.
有任务给你
Bringing a homework assignment for you,
打开实验室
so open the lab.
遵命
Do tell.
我们五分钟后到
Engage in five minutes.
通话完毕
Get off the radio.
怎么回事
Well, what is it?
别说了 米尔顿
Now, Milton.
- 米琼恩 - 我在
- Michonne? - Right here.
举着
Hold that.
为什么把我们关在这
Why are we being held here?
- 让我们走 - 你还没恢复
- We want to leave. - You're not well enough.
而且天都黑了 你该留下过夜
And it's dark. You should stay the night.
我们在哪
Where are we?
我不能说
That's not for me to say.
- 他会找你谈的 - 谁
- He'll talk to you. - Who?
看看别的病人去 医生
Go check on your patient, Doc.
我还活着 你肯定难以置信
Bet you was wondering if I was real.
你大概希望我死了吧
Probably hoping I wasn't.
但我命大
Well, here I am.
看来世界比起以前变小了啊
I guess this old world gets a little smaller toward the end, huh?
活人越来越少了 不是吗
Ain't so many of us left to share the air, right?
他们找到我的时候
You know, when they found me,
我失血过多 快不行了
I was near bled out.
饥肠辘辘
Starving.
心里想着
Thinking to myself a bullet.
自杀了事可能是最好的结局
might make a good last meal.
死了就能好好休息了
Take myself a nice long nap after.
在另一个世界等着达里尔
Wait for Daryl on the other side.
你见过我弟弟吗
You seen my brother?
很长时间没见了
Not for a long time.
我也是
Makes two of us.
他回去找你了
He went back for you.
他和瑞克
Him and Rick.
但是你已经离开了
You were already gone.
其实
Well…
我没有全身而退
not all of me.
是啊 瑞克
Yeah, Rick.
就是他那个混球把我拷在屋顶上
He's that prick that cuffed me to the rooftop.
是的
Yeah.
他努力补救了
He tried.
达里尔也知道
Daryl saw that.
我弟弟比我温和善良
He's always been the sweet one, my baby brother.
他想要继续找你
He wanted to keep looking,
但是发生了很多事 有人牺牲
but things happen. People died.
很多人都死了
A lot of them.
吉姆 戴尔
Jim, Dale,
杰奎 索菲亚
Jacqui, Sophia…
艾米
Amy.
你妹妹吗
Your sister?
是的
Yes.
她是个好孩子
She was a good kid.
听到这个消息我很遗憾
I'm sorry to hear it.
还有其他人死了 很多人
There were more. A lot more.
我们不得不离开亚特兰大
We had to leave Atlanta.
我们最终在一个农场落脚
We wind up on a farm.
达里尔站了出来
Daryl stepped up.
成了团队里不可或缺的重要成员
Became a valued member of the group.
现在他死了
Now he's dead.
我也不能确定
I don't know that for sure.
我们被尸群攻击后逃跑了
We got run off by a herd.
多长时间了
How long ago?
七八个月
Seven, eight months.
我和其他人走散了
I was separated from the rest of them.
被落下了
Got left behind.
我明白你的感受
I know what it feels like.
我表示怀疑
I doubt that.
你想从我们这得到什么
What do you want from us?
该死
Damn.
她坐在那里
There she sits,
四周有墙 头上有屋顶
four walls around her, roof over her head,
血管里输着药
medicine in her veins,
她还想知道我想从她那得到什么
and she wants to know what I want from her.
我帮你和你的哑巴朋友脱离苦海 美女
I plucked you and your mute here out of the dirt, blondie.
救了你们的小命
Saved your asses.
就换不来一声谢谢吗
How about a thank you?
你用枪指着我们
You had a gun on us.
哑巴说话了
Ooh, she speaks.
过去一年里谁没被枪指过啊
Who ain't had a gun on 'em in the past year, huh?
举手示意一下
Show of hands, y'all.
有人吗
Anybody? Hmm?
香珀特 克罗利
Shumpert, Crowley.
你们被枪指过吗
Y'all had a gun on y'all?
见鬼
Hell…
如果有个陌生人
I think I'd piss my pants.
手揣在兜里向我走来 我会吓得尿裤子的
if some stranger come walking up with his mitts in his pockets.
那才是你们真正应该害怕的
That'd be the son of a bitch you'd really want to be scared of.
谢谢你
Thank you.
当然
Sure thing.
感觉怎么样
How you feeling?
把武器还我们
We want our weapons.
当然可以
Sure.
出去的路上就可以拿到
On our way out the front gates.
带我们出去
Show us the way.
你一直把我们锁在这个屋子里
You've kept us locked up in this room.
你们看见窗户上有栏杆了吗
You see any bars on the windows?
我们一直对你们仔细照料
You're being cared for.
是严加监视
Under guard.
这是为了保护我们的人 我们不了解你们
To protect our people. We don't know you.
我们对你的了解够多了 不想再待下去了
We know enough about you to want out of this place.
我们亲眼见你把刀插进两个死人的头颅中
We watched you drive a knife into the skulls of two dead men.
那又是怎么回事
What the hell was that all about?
他们变成行尸了
They turned.
他们又没被咬
They weren't bitten.
那不重要
Doesn't matter.
不管什么死法 我们都会变成行尸
However we die, we all turn.
我解除了他们的痛苦
I put them out of their misery.
开始很难接受 但这就是事实
It's not easy news to swallow at first, but there it is.
你们不是囚犯 你们是贵客
You're not prisoners here, you're guests.
如果你们想离开 我说过 请自便
If you want to leave, as I said, you're free to do so.
但是我们傍晚后不会开门
But we don't open the gates past dusk.
容易吸引行尸
Draws too much attention.
尤其是你 你需要好好睡一觉
And you especially, you need a solid night's sleep.
你的状况已经不能再多撑一天了
You wouldn't last another day out there in your condition.
明早有人会把你们带到我那儿
Have you brought over to my place in the morning.
把武器还给你
Return your weapons.
我会给你额外的武器和食物
Extra ammo, food for the road,
一些药品 如果需要再给你辆车
some meds, keys to a vehicle if you want one.
很快送你们上路
Send you on your way.
不必多虑
No hard feelings.
欢迎来伍德伯里
Welcome to Woodbury.
跟我来
Come with me.
去后门跟皮特换岗
Go relieve Pete at the back gate.
去操作探照灯
Take the spotlight.
你们是军队吗
Are you military?
不算是 有几个老兵
Hardly. Couple of vets,
但是总的来说我们是自编队伍
but by and large we're self-trained.
他们拿的可是重武器
That's heavy artillery they're packing.
有些人来时带着枪
Some men arrive with guns,
但大多数武器都是四处搜集的
but most of the weapons are scavenged over time.
镇子的另一边呢 其他的街道呢
And the other side of town? The rest of the streets?
都像这里一样严防紧守吗
They're all guarded like this?
不可能的
It can't be.
可能的
It can.
而且事实确实如此
and it is.
看到一个行尸 总督
Got us a creeper, Governor.
我可以用一下吗
May I?
谢谢
Thank you.
总督 他们这么叫你吗
Governor? They call you that?
有些绰号改不了 不管你想不想
Some nicknames stick whether you want them to or not.
「寸头」才是绰号 「总督」可是个头衔
Buzz is a nickname. Governor is a title.
二者不同
There's a difference.
打中了
Got him.
他有几个行尸伙伴
He brought his buddies.
安全了
Clear.
我们明早去处理尸体
We'll get them in the morning.
不能让尸体烂在外面
Can't leave them to rot.
那样会有味道 让大家闻起来不好受
Creates an odor. Makes people uneasy.
什么大家 这里没人
What people? There's nobody here.
这是个空镇子
It's a ghost town.
走这边
This way.
你在这儿会更舒服
You'll be more comfortable here.
这儿不是四季酒店 但能洗热水澡
Not the Four Seasons, but there's a hot shower.
水源有限 尽快洗完
Water's limited, so keep it short.
我们有食物 水源 干净衣服
We got food, water, fresh clothes.
希望你们满意
Hope this works.
我知道你带着刀感觉更好
I know you'd feel better with your sword,
更有安全感 但是在这儿你很安全
more secure, but you're safe here.
非常感谢
We appreciate it.
那个飞行员怎样了 他能活下来吗
What about the pilot? Will he make it?
斯蒂文斯医生会尽她所能
Well, Dr. Stevens is doing all she can.
我知道你有很多问题 但是我还有事
Now, I know you got a lot more questions, but I got work to do.
如果你需要什么 我的人就在门外
My man will be outside the door if you need anything else.
明天见
I'll see you tomorrow.
这是真的
It's real.
你俩在外太久了
You two were out there for a long time.
你们在外面求生时 总督在发展这个镇子
While you were, the Governor was doing this.
这里有多少人
How many people do you have here?
七十三个
73.
艾琳要生了 有了孩子就是七十四个
Eileen's about to pop, so her kid will make it 74.
还在慢慢发展中
It's still a work in progress,
罗马也不是一天建成的
but Rome wasn't built in a day.
真是大胆的类比
That's a bold comparison.
我们很自豪
I think we've earned it.
有一个多月没有行尸越过围墙了
Walls haven't been breached in well over a month.
初冬开始内部就没有伤亡人员了
We haven't suffered a casualty on the inside since early winter.
这怎么可能
How's that possible?
总督设立了严格的门禁
Our Governor set a strict curfew.
天黑后谁都不能出门
Nobody out after dark.
声响和光亮都尽量避免
Noise and light are kept to the bare minimum.
围墙上有武装警卫巡视四周
Armed guards on the fence and patrolling the perimeter.
让行尸无法靠近
to keep the biters away.
昨晚进城时 我看到你们的巡逻队的所为了
I saw what your patrols do on the way in last night.
他们把死尸挂起来 像装饰品一样
They had a dead one strung up like an ornament.
我不会为他们辩解
I won't make excuses,
但那些人每天都冒着生命危险
but those men put their lives at risk every day.
来保护这个镇
to protect this town.
他们失去的不只是朋友
They've lost more than a few friends out there.
每人都以自己的方式应对
Everybody copes in their own way.
但我会跟总督说说
But I'll raise it with the Governor.
那个地方井然有序
Things were orderly.
四周筑有围栏
The fences held.
人们受到保护
People were protected.
并有充足的食物和贮备
Food and supplies were lasting.
之后营地中一人被咬伤
Then one of the men inside got bit.
具体情况尚不清楚
Not sure how.
接着他失去控制
He went haywire.
营地顿时一片恐慌
Panic swept through the camp.
有人从大门逃了出去
Someone opened the gate to escape,
其他人被咬伤感染
others were bitten and infected.
人们乱作一团
Those people went crazy.
整个地方在几小时内变成人间地狱
The whole place went to hell in a few hours.
我们小队带上补给
My team grabbed whatever supplies and vehicles we could.
开车逃离了岗哨
and abandoned our post.
你们中有多少人逃了出来
How many of you escaped?
我们小队有十人
There was 10 in my group.
大约逃到六十里开外
We got maybe 60 miles from the post.
堵在公路上无法前行
before getting jammed up on the highway.
然后我开飞机侦察前方情况
I took the bird up in the air to scout ahead.
直升机在骚乱中受损 但我们别无选择
She took a beating in the riot, but we had no choice.
我的伙伴呢
My guys?
没活下来
No.
我去找余下的人
Let me go find the rest.
把他们带到这个安全的地方
Bring them here where they'll be safe.
他们在那里等你
They're out there waiting for you.
没人保护他们
exposed.
告诉我他们在哪儿 我保证
Tell me where they are, and I promise,
只要他们还活着
if they're still alive,
就把他们带回来
I'll bring 'em in.
任务完成了吗
Did you finish your homework?
不巧 被狗耽搁了
Unfortunately, the dog's eating it already.
你叫我什么
What the hell you call me?
这里是学校操场吗
Hey, where are we, back in the school yard?
怎么 你还得势不饶人了
What, you want to take his lunch money while you're at it?
抱歉 总督
Sorry, Governor.
也许我在你身上纯属浪费时间
Maybe I've wasted my time with you.
也许你还是没长记性
Maybe you haven't learned anything at all.
- 他还想在这儿抽烟 - 你也没好到哪去
- He was trying to smoke in here. - And you, I expect better.
去招惹熊只会被抓伤
Keep poking the bear and you're bound to get mauled.
记好了 跟我说说那个女孩的事儿
Remember that. Tell me about the girl.
- 她叫安德莉亚 - 你认识她
- Name's Andrea. - You know her?
她是亚特兰大那伙人中的
She from that group in Atlanta?
嗯
Yeah.
就是他们那伙人把我留在屋顶
Same one left me on the roof,
害我不得不截肢
forced me to mutilate myself.
她认识你弟弟达里尔吗
Does she know your brother Daryl?
是的 认识
Yeah, she did.
那再找她谈谈
Then talk to her again.
看还能知道些什么
See what else you can find out.
给我看看你的成果
Show me something.
研究的怎么样了
What do you make of it?
令我大吃一惊 真的
Oh, pretty impressive, really.
很有创意
Major kudos for ingenuity.
把它们的胳膊拿掉 它们就没法抓你
Take away their arms so they can't grab you.
把它们的下颚拿掉 它们就没法咬你
Take away their jaws so they can't bite you.
让它们丧失咬人的能力
Take away their ability to eat,
它们就会失去进食的欲望
they lose interest in doing so.
也就不会再攻击人
They're no longer in attack mode.
即使它们在身边 我们也不会有危险
We can be in their presence without threat.
它们在某种程度上变温顺了
They're… they become docile in a sense.
潜行者
Lurkers.
乖乖尸
Mm, docile.
或是潜行者 随你怎么说
Or lurkers. You know, whatever you like.
为什么留着它们
Why keep 'em?
像驱虫剂
Ah, repellent.
作为伪装
Camouflage.
与行尸同行
Walk with the biters,
它们就会认为你也是行尸
they think you're a biter.
低调 妙招
Low profile. That's smart.
它们还很瘦
They're still pretty thin.
如果它们不吃东西 为什么不会饿死
If they're not eating, why don't they starve?
它们会饿
They are starving.
只是来的比我们慢得多
They just do it slower than we do.
我们似乎在用常识解释非常识现象
Feels like we're trying to impose logic on chaos.
这未尝不是件好事
That is not a bad thing.
是的 但这对我们又有什么好处
No, but what does it buy us?
更多的疑问 更多的假设
More questions, more theories,
却没有答案
no answers.
现在还没有
Not yet.
如果我可以和这两个女人谈谈
If I could talk to those women…
莫尔正在和她们谈
Merle's handling it.
我不是想质疑你的判断力 总督
I don't want to question your judgment, Governor.
你可以质疑
Sure, you do.
这正是我需要你的理由
That's why I need you.
你的质疑 还有你泡的茶
That and your tea.
好吧
Well, then.
恕我直言
With all due respect,
让莫尔不受监控去和她们谈话是个错误
letting Merle talk to those women unsupervised is a mistake.
你经常说 每套工具里都要有一把锤子
Now, you've always said every tool kit needs a hammer,
你真的认为锤子适合这项工作吗
but do you really feel the hammer is the right tool for that job?
八个月吗
Eight months?
难以想象两位女士在外生存了这么久
Hard to believe you ladies lasted so long out there.
就因为我们是女的吗
Because we're women?
因为你们孤立无援
Because you were alone.
我们可以彼此照顾
We had each other.
两个人对抗整个末世
Two against the world.
生存机会可不大
It's long odds.
我们可以应付
We managed.
- 太了不起了 - 同意
- Oh, we're impressed. - Very.
要在野外生存可不是件容易的事
Survival in the wild is tough sledding.
每天清早在地上一睁开眼
Wake up every morning on the ground wondering.
就怕这是自己的最后一天
if today is the day.
究竟会是个痛快的死法
Will it be quick and final.
还是慢慢地死去 永受折磨
or slow and, well, without end?
会不会有人照我的脑袋来上一下
Will someone have the good sense to kill my brain,
或者我也会变成僵尸中的一员
or will I come back as one of them?
你认为僵尸们是否也会有记忆
Do you think they remember anything?
回忆起它们自己的过去
The person they once were?
我可不想考虑这些问题
I don't think about it.
米尔顿认为它们的记忆或许
Milton believes there might be a trace of the person they were.
还在脑中萦绕
still trapped inside.
就像回声一样
Like an echo.
我想你可能也这样想过
Surely it must have crossed your mind.
有那么一会想过
At one time, yeah.
在它试图咬死我之前
Right before it tried to bite me.
然后你就杀了它
And then you killed it?
我说「它」是因为
I say "It" Only because no one here.
我想这里没有人想称呼为「他」
likes to refer to them as him…
或者「她」
or her. Ahem.
你用链子锁起来的那两个 它们是谁
The two you had in chains, who were they?
你控制它们的独特方法
The way you controlled them,
让它们为你所用
used them to your benefit.
你应该认识它们吧
You did know them, didn't you?
让她们安静地吃吧
Let them eat.
抱歉
My apologies.
你觉得你能守住这个地方吗
So what you have here, you expect it to hold?
万一尸群经过怎么办
What if a herd comes through?
我们能守住
It'll hold.
你有什么秘诀
What's your secret?
高大的城墙
Really big walls.
那些军人也曾有高墙
That soldier had walls, too,
他们的结局我们都很清楚
and we all know how that turned out.
你说的也对
I guess we do.
真正的秘诀在于墙内
The real secret is what goes on within these walls.
要让人们意识到自己的本性
It's about getting back to who we were.
找回真正的自我
Who we really are.
军人们只是在企盼救援
They're just waiting to be saved.
这里的人们却有自己的家 有医疗服务
And people here have homes, medical care,
孩子们可以上学 大人们拥有工作
kids go to school, adults have jobs to do.
一切都有条不紊 就像一个社区
There's a sense of purpose. We're a community.
还有很多枪和弹药
With a lot of guns and ammunition.
- 总比没有好 - 还有高大的城墙
- Never hurts. - And really big walls.
为了保卫家园我们无所畏惧
And men willing to risk everything to defend them.
危及这里的安全
Compromise our safety,
毁掉我们的社区
destroy our community,
我宁死也不会让这一切发生
I'll die before I'll let that happen.
看上去你像在尘世之外过着悠闲的生活
Looks like you're sitting pretty at the end of the world.
我看上去很悠闲吗
Do I strike you as the kind of man who sits pretty?
种何因 得何果
You reap what you sow.
我们付出了耕耘
We're the seed.
冬天已过 是时候收获成果了
Now winter has passed, it's time to harvest.
这怕只是空想吧
Time in a hope?
我们会夺回曾经属于我们的一切
We're going out there and we're taking back what's ours.
人类文明
Civilization.
必将重新崛起
We will rise again.
只是这次 我们不会撕咬对方
Only this time we won't be eating each other.
为重振文明干杯
To civilization, then.
不好意思
Excuse me.
茶怎么样
How's the tea?
抱歉 早饭要提早结束 有急事
Sorry to cut breakfast short, but this can't wait.
把武器还我们
We want our weapons.
我们可以让你们把食物外带
Well, we can make this meal to go.
武器也可以双手奉上
and your weapons will be waiting outside,
但是你应该先放松一下
but you should take time to relax.
恢复下体力
Get your strength back.
四处逛逛 谁知道呢
Have a look around. Who knows?
你们说不定会喜欢这里
You might like what you see.
我不信任他
I don't trust him.
为什么不
Why not?
你有信任过别人吗
Have you ever trusted anybody?
有过
Yeah.
就花一两天的时间试试 我就这点要求
Then give this a day or two, that's all I'm asking.
刚好可以让我们休整一下
Some time to get our shit together.
我很好 不用休整
My shit never stopped being together.
米尔顿询问你的行尸时你可不淡定
Didn't look that way when Milton asked about your walkers.
你还好没用叉子戳他眼睛
I'm surprised he didn't get a fork in his eye.
我的行尸关他鸟事
It was none of his damn business.
大概也不关我事吧
I guess it's none of mine, either.
我们在一起七个月了 经历了风风雨雨
Seven months together, all we've been through,
我还是觉得不怎么了解你
I still feel like I hardly know you.
对不起 这是事实 你了解我的一切
I'm sorry, it's the truth. Come on. You know everything about me.
你了解的够多了
You know enough.
那些行尸整个冬天都和我们在一起
Those walkers were with us all winter long,
保护着我们 你却毫不犹豫地杀死它们
protecting us, and you took them out without any hesitation.
- 那已经 - 我比你想象的心狠
- That had… - It was easier than you think.
有车接近 下士
Vehicle approaching, Corporal.
保持警戒
All right, stay alert.
别开枪
Hey, hey, hey, hey! Don't shoot!
报上你的身份
Identify yourself.
我们发现了你们的人
Hey, hey, hey, hey! We found your guy.
韦尔斯中尉
Wells. Lieutenant Wells.
他的直升机迫降了
His chopper went down.
他在哪
Where is he?
他在我们住处 他受了重伤
We got a little settlement. Now, he's badly hurt.
但他还活着
But he's alive.
其他人都死了 我很遗憾
The other guys didn't make it, I'm sorry.
韦尔斯说我能在这里找到你们
But Wells, he told me I would find you here.
他让我带你们去见他
Wants me to bring you to him.
韦尔斯在他们那里 他们找到了他
They found Wells. They got him. They found him.
当然 我们也找到了你们
We sure did. We found you, too.
永远别浪费子弹 孩子
Never waste a bullet, son.
把武器都拿走
Pick up the rest of these weapons.
遵命长官
Yes, sir.
去给那个年轻人解除痛苦吧
Go put a merciful end to that young man's days.
看看大兵们都有什么好东西 好吗
Let's see what Uncle Sam brought us, shall we?
昨天我们带回了三名新人
We brought in three new people yesterday.
其中一位是国民警卫队的直升机驾驶员
One was a helicopter pilot with a National Guard outfit.
在他弥留之际
Even though he's clinging to life,
他告诉我们在高速路上还有他伙伴
he told us about his convoy on the highway,
他的战友
his men.
我向他保证 把他们活着救回来
I promised I'd bring them back here alive.
但他们没有像我们一样的高墙
But they didn't have our walls.
或栅栏
or our fences.
行尸在我们之前找到了他们
Biters got there before we did.
他们拥有卡车 车上有武器
Now, the men had trucks, the trucks had weapons,
食物和药品 都是我们需要的
food, medicine, things we need.
我们虽然不认识他们
Now, we didn't know them,
但唯有珍惜我们拥有的一切
but we'll honor their sacrifice.
才是对他们牺牲最大的敬意
by not taking what we have here for granted.
快天黑了 大家都回家吧
Won't be long before dark, so go on home.
对你们拥有的一切要心存感激
Be thankful for what you have.
互相照顾
Watch out for each other.
你还没走
You're still here.
有什么我能帮忙的吗
Anything I can do?
没有 今晚没有
No, nothing tonight.
漫长的一天吧
Long day?
最近没有一天不漫长
Haven't had many short ones lately.
晚安
Good night.
如果你不介意
So what's your real name?
请问你真名叫什么
If it's not asking too much.
我绝不告诉别人
I never tell.
凡事无绝对
Never say never.
绝不
Never.